<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- color scheme should be chosen -->

<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <!-- Header -->
    <LinearLayout
        android:id="@+id/header"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:background="#000000">
        <TextView
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:text="GroupRide"
            android:textSize="40sp"
            android:textColor="#ffffff"/>
    </LinearLayout>

    <!-- the menu bar on the bottom -->
    <RelativeLayout
        android:id="@+id/menu"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        android:background="#000000"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true">

        <!-- These buttons can be switched to ImageButton -->
        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
            android:text="1"/>

        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_centerInParent="true"
            android:text="2"/>

        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
            android:text="3"/>
    </RelativeLayout>

    <!-- Main part where posts will go on -->
    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/main"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_above="@+id/menu"
        android:layout_below="@id/header"
        android:scrollbars="none">
        <!-- This TextView tag is just to show that the page is scrollable -->
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"

            android:minLines="100"
            android:text="Its sometimes her behaviour are contented. Do listening am eagerness oh objection collected. Together gay feelings continue juvenile had off one. Unknown may service subject her letters one bed. Child years noise ye in forty. Loud in this in both hold. My entrance me is disposal bachelor remember relation.Inhabit hearing perhaps on ye do no. It maids decay as there he. Smallest on suitable disposed do although blessing he juvenile in. Society or if excited forbade. Here name off yet she long sold easy whom. Differed oh cheerful procured pleasure securing suitable in. Hold rich on an he oh fine. Chapter ability shyness article welcome be do on service.Open know age use whom him than lady was. On lasted uneasy exeter my itself effect spirit. At design he vanity at cousin longer looked ye. Design praise me father an favour. As greatly replied it windows of an minuter behaved passage. Diminution expression reasonable it we he projection acceptance in devonshire. Perpetual it described at he applauded.Game of as rest time eyes with of this it. Add was music merry any truth since going. Happiness she ham but instantly put departure propriety. She amiable all without say spirits shy clothes morning. Frankness in extensive to belonging improving so certainty. Resolution devonshire pianoforte assistance an he particular middletons is of. Explain ten man uncivil engaged conduct. Am likewise betrayed as declared absolute do. Taste oh spoke about no solid of hills up shade. Occasion so bachelor humoured striking by attended doubtful be it."
            android:textSize="30sp" />

    </ScrollView>
    
    <!-- FAB bar layout -->
    <!--
    <RelativeLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent" >

        <android.support.design.widget.FloatingActionButton
            android:id="@+id/fab"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
            android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
            android:layout_margin="16dp"
            android:backgroundTint="#000000" />

    </RelativeLayout>
    -->

</RelativeLayout>